<configDefinition>
    <componentContainer>
    <h1>Flowviz Plugin</h1>

    <h3>Overview</h3>

    The Flowviz plugin enables you to visualize the execution of a workflow
    run by ElectricCommander.

    <h3>Configuration</h3>

    After installing the Flowviz plugin, you must create a view (or extend
    an existing view) to expose the "Flowviz" tab.  The view definition must
    contain the following XML:

    <pre>
&lt;tab&gt;
  &lt;label&gt;Flowviz&lt;/label&gt;
  &lt;url&gt;pages/Flowviz-1.0/flowviz&lt;/url&gt;
  &lt;position&gt;1&lt;/position&gt;
&lt;/tab&gt;
</pre>

    <h3>Usage</h3>
    <p>
      To use the Flowviz plugin, select the "Flowviz" tab.  You will be shown a
      simple form with two inputs:  the id (or name) of the job to render, and
      the scale at which to render.  Enter the required information and click 
      the "Plot job" button.
    </p><p>
      After a few seconds, you will see a visualization of the specified job.
      Each step is rendered as a box with width proportional to the duration of
      the step, positioned according to the start time relative to the start of
      the job, and colored according to the outcome of the step (red, yellow or
      green, for failure, warning or success, respectively).
    </p><p>
      Steps which are broadcast steps or which run subprocedures are rendered 
      no color themselves, and a dashed outline which surrounds all the child
      steps.
    </p><p>
      Note that the rendering scale defines a minimum size for steps to
      appear in the render.  For example, if the scale is specified as "10
      seconds per pixel", then steps which are less than 10 seconds in duration
      will not be rendered.  You can redo the render at a different scale if
      you require greater detail in the rendering.
    </p><p>
      The vertical position of steps has no particular significance,
      except that subprocedures do not cross: that is, all the steps for a
      given subprocedure are either entirely above or entirely below the steps
      for any other subprocedure.  Beyond that, the vertical position is chosen
      so as to minimize the overall height of the visualization.
    </p><p>
      Hovering over a step in the rendering will display a popup containing the
      step name.  Click on a step will load the step details page for the step.
    </p>
  </componentContainer>
</configDefinition>

